Class of 1950 Records, 1946-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1950 Records
1946-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1950.
RG 80 UUID:e4a14201-5577-414f-af82-92eea2244025
8 boxes (3.2 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1950.
The Class of 1950 was the seventy-second graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1950 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1950, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, questionnaires, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1950 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 1)
- Commencement-Dramatics 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 2)
- Commencement-Music 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 3)
- Commencement-Photographs 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 4)
- Commencement-Photographs 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 5)
- Commencement-Speaker 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 6)
- Freshman Dance 1947 (Box 2171, Folder 7)
- Freshman Handbook 1946-1947 (Box 2171, Folder 8)
- General 1947, 1968 (Box 2171, Folder 9)
- Groups 1946-1950 (Box 2171, Folder 10)
- Hoop Rolling 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 11)
- Ivy Day 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 12)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 13)
- Junior Prom 1949 (Box 2171, Folder 14)
- Junior Ushers 1949 (Box 2171, Folder 15)
- Class Letters 1960-1976 (Box 2171, Folder 16)
- Class Newsletter 1996-2002 (Box 2171, Folder 17)
- Officers 1947 (Box 2171, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1951 (Box 2171, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1955 (Box 2171, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1960 (Box 2171, Folder 21)
- Reunions 1965 (Box 2171, Folder 22)
- Reunions 1970 (Box 2171, Folder 23)
- Reunions 1975 (Box 2171, Folder 24)
- Reunions 1980 (Box 2171, Folder 25)
- Reunions-45th 1995 (Box 2171, Folder 26)
  (See individual box)
- Senior Prom 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 27)
- Senior Song 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 28)
- Sophomore Carnival 1948 (Box 2171, Folder 29)
- Step Sings 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 30)
- Class Supper 1950 (Box 2171, Folder 31)
- 45th Reunion-Miscellaneous 1995 (Box 2171.1, Folder 1)
- Reunion Questionnaires 1995 (Box 2171.1, Folder 2)
- Reunion Questionnaires 1995 (Box 2171.1, Folder 3)
- Reunion Questionnaire-note on restrictions 1995 (Box 2171.1, Folder 4)
- Reunion Questionnaire-Script with Statistics and Comments 1995 (Box 2171.1, Folder 5)
- 50th Reunion Book 2000 (Box 2171.2, Folder 1)